rojkmao.com 2019-02-10

# PRIVACY POLICY | RojKmao

## **We are happy to see you at this website and hope that you will enjoy the information given on our website.**

* * *

## PRIVACY POLICY : –

This page confirms my ownership of the site and that this site adheres to Google AdSense program policies & Terms and Conditions. At [RojKmao.com](https://www.rojkmao.com/) , the privacy of our visitors is of most importance to us.

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by us and how it is used.

## **In terms of Log Files : –**

Like many other Web sites, we [RojKmao.com](https://www.rojkmao.com/) makes use of log files.

The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## **In terms of Cookies and Web beacons : –**

[RojKmao.com](https://www.rojkmao.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.We have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

## **Sharing Your Personal Information :-**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## **Your Acceptance Of These Terms :-**

By using this Site [RojKmao.com](https://www.rojkmao.com/) ,  you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
